(Raj:)Oh.
(Howard:)Go away, Sheldon.
There's a $9.95 e-book
down the drain.
(Raj:)What's in the bag?
(Sheldon:)It's for Howard.
(Howard:)Oh. Sheldon, you can't
fix this with gifts.
(Sheldon:)Nevertheless, I've hurt you,
(Sheldon:)and whether you
forgive me or not,
(Raj:)I want you to
have this.
(Howard:)You're giving me
a couch cushion?
(Leonard:)No.
(Sheldon:)The cushion is merely symbolic.
(Sheldon:)I'm giving you my spot
on the couch.
(Howard:)But you love that spot.
(Sheldon:)No. I love my mother.
(Sheldon:)My feelings for my spot
are much greater.
(Sheldon:)It is the singular location
in space
(Sheldon:)around which revolves
my entire universe.
(Sheldon:)And now it's yours.
(Raj:)Oh, my God, dude.
Now you have to forgive him.
(Woman at Door:)All right.
(Sheldon:)Apology accepted.
(Sheldon:)High five.
(Sheldon:)Not too hard.
(Woman at Door:)Thank you.
I haven't cried like this
since Toy Story 3.
(Howard:)I got to tell you,
(Howard:)Sheldon, I understand why
you chose this spot.
(Howard:)I mean, the temperature is
good, but there's no draft.
(Howard:)I can see the television,
but I can still talk to...
(Sheldon:)I changed my mind.
Get out of my spot.
(Penny:)How long?
(Leonard:)94 seconds.